

CURICULUM VITAE

Abdul hamid hwalla

PROFILE

My Full Name Is Abdul Hamid Azzam Hwalla I am 27 Years Old Born In 29/1/1994 In Tripoli Lebanon.

I Have Superior Technician Diploma in Accounting, Technical Baccalaureate Diploma in Accounting and Informatics With 7 Years of Experience.

PS: fully vaccinated (Pfizer)

CONTACT



aboudhwalla@gmail.com



+96171836727



Lebanon, Tripoli

language

Language	Writing	Reading
Arabic	Excellent	Excellent
English	Excellent	Excellent
French	Good	Good

COMPUTER Skills

- MS Office
- > All Accounting Software
- Node is , Html , Java script , CSS

EDUCATION

> Al Fayhaa institute

<u>Superior Technician Diploma</u> - Auditing and experience in accounting 2018-2019

(A state certificate equivalent to a bachelor's degree)

Zgharta Technical Industrial

<u>Technical Baccalaureate Diploma</u> – Accounting and informatics 2015-2016

-Brevet 2008-2009

EXPERIENCE

Currently, I am working in two jobs

- 1-Hajar company (wholesale stationers) Tripoli
- -Data Entry from 2012 till 2014
- -Accountant from 2014 till 2017
 - preparing accounts and tax returns.
 - administering payrolls and controlling income and expenditure.
 - auditing financial information.
 - Compiling and presenting reports, budgets, business plans, commentaries and financial statements.
 - analysing accounts and business plans.
- -sales manager and Accountant from 2017 till now
- 2-Collège 3G (School in Al minyah, north Lebanon)
- -Part time accountant from 2020 till now